lootbargain.com 2015-12-29

# Loot Bargain

Lootbargain.com strives to protect your (the “user”) personal information. Maintaining your online privacy is important for us. Thus, Lootbargain.com safeguards it through this Privacy Policy that applies to all the information collected or received by the Website (“we”, “us” or “our”). Our Privacy Policy regulates our practices of collecting, using and sharing your personal identifiable information. Abiding to the Indian laws, we will not use your personal data for any commercial gain. We will also not release your personal identifiable information without your consent at any point in time. 

**PLEASE READ ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE. BY USING OR ACCESSING THIS SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE YOUR APPROVAL TO ALL THE CONDITIONS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY. YOU MUST WITHDRAW FROM THIS SITE IMMEDIATELY, IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE FOLLOWING TERMS.**

  1. Modification of Privacy Policy

We reserve the sole right to change this privacy policy at any time in future. All such modifications will be posted to this page as well as to other appropriate pages to inform you about our latest privacy practices. You will be informed about any material changes made to the privacy statement through a notice on the home page or a personal email.

Please do keep visiting the website frequently to keep a check on the changes made to this privacy policy. 

  2. Types and Uses of Collected Information

The information that we collect about you can be divided under two heads: (a.) Personally Identifiable Information and (b.) Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

The term ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ refers to the data that identifies a particular user of the website. There are many instances where you knowingly share your personal information with us. As a user of our website, you may choose to communicate with us via emails, forums, surveys, polls, comments and contests. This is just an optional activity for you and you are free to not share your personal information. However, if you engage in our forums, contests or other activities, we may ask you to submit your email address, full name, postal address, telephone number etc. We also ask for your credit card number and its details when you order any products or services from our website. 

All such information submitted by you may be used by us for any internal business causes like market research and product improvement. Moreover, this information can also be used for resolving disputes, troubleshooting problems and enforcing various agreements with you from time to time. We also may share this information with our other affiliates. Lastly, your email and postal address details may be used to communicate with you regarding the promotion of products and services offered by us.

‘Referral Service’ is another instance through which we gather information. This service includes ‘Buy it for a Friend’, ‘Tell-A-Friend’ type of things, where you need to submit the personal information of your friend when you indulge in a deal for him/her. We send your friend the gift purchased by you along with an email or else invite him/her to visit our website. This type of information is simply stored for sending a gift, a single email or for measuring the success level of a referral program.

When we speak of ‘Non-Personally Identifiable Information’, we refer to the information that does not straight away identify the end user. When you browse through our website, without revealing your name, email ID or any other information, we collect and store some kind of information about your visit. This automatically saved information includes your IP address, the time and date you accessed our website as well as the type of OS (Operating system) and browser used by you. Additionally, our system also records the history of pages that you click-through and the address or the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the previously visited website.

The Non-Personally Identifiable Information is used by us to administer the website, gather demographic details/data, analyze trends and comply with legal terms. Along with using this information internally, we also may share it with the advertisers or third party service providers in order to evaluate the overall impact of our online advertising package. 

  1. • Releasing Personally Identifiable Information

We do not share, trade, sell or rent your Personally Identifiable Information with any third party except in the following instances: 

    1. **Sharing Information with Lootbargain Merchants:** As an integral part of our services, we offer deals from various merchants referred to as “Lootbargain Merchants”, who need to access the information about our customers in order to fulfill redemption. This type of sharing of information enables the Lootbargain Merchant to reach you directly if they wish to do so. Anyhow, we share your Personally Identifiable Information with a merchant only if you are involved in an identification activity and we do not hold any liability for any actions of the Lootbargain Merchants, other than product promotion.

    2. **Sharing Information With Third Party Service Providers**  
We rely on the authorized third party service providers for performing a lot of functions on our behalf. So we may share your Personally Identifiable Information with them in order to complete orders, administer contests, send emails, analyze data, process payments made by credit card, remove repetitive information, provide customer service, operate the website and troubleshoot problems.

    3. **Remarketing Your Information**  
Through remarketing we connect with those customers who have already dealt with us in the past. Here, we make use of the past interaction with the existing or precedent customers. We may hire third party vendors to facilitate our remarketing services. These third-party vendors like Google utilize cookies to advertise our offerings on the basis of your previous visits to Lootbargain.com. However, this sharing of information is only meant for accomplishing the remarketing tasks and will not be used elsewhere. 

    4. **Transfer of Business**  
It is common for any company to get acquired by or be merged with another company in future. If this ever happens with Lootbargain.com, the data containing your Personally Identification Information will be automatically transferred to the successor company. Nevertheless, the privacy policy for such information would remain the same.

    5. **Protection**  
We may release your Personally identifiable Information as per the legal requirements to guard our own rights or else to abide by a court order, legal process or a judicial proceeding served on Lootbargain.com. We may also disclose such information for the enforcement of this privacy policy, for applying the terms of use, to ensure the safety of our website or to protect the rights of our website, users or other people.

  2. • Releasing Non-Personally Identifiable information

We may share non-Personally Identifiable Information with our affiliates, partners and advertisers if required. The advertisers may need the aggregated demographic data for different purposes. Such Non-Personally Identifiable Information includes the history of your visits to serve advertisements through network tags. 

Some of our third-party advertising companies may be a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), which is one of the advertising networks. So if you want to stay away from the advertising messages of NAI members, you must click: http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp

At times, we also may rely upon the Third Party Service Providers to analyze and record Non Personally Identifiable Information related with usage and volume statistics for administrative and developmental purposes. This information may also be published for promotion of a product or service. For your information, this data is just a generic summary of the user activities, collected by the third party for our internal usage.

  1. Correction and Revision of Information  
We appreciate your involvement with our website and thus we enable you to revise and edit your Personally Identifiable Information. You are free to change or update such information from time to time. You may update your details by logging into your account or drop us a mail with your name, email ID, address along with the information that you wish to update.   
You must update your Personally Identifiable Information whenever it changes and you can also ask for the information of your deleted account. Since we keep a record of all the past transactions, we can provide you with such information as and when required. As a matter of fact, it is practically impossible to delete all your account information due to our practice of periodically backing-up information. Anyhow, if you agree to store your credit card information, it will be stored on a safe page. Such information can be deleted by going to your profile’s ‘my account’ section. 

  2. Protection of Information  
Since we are serious about maintaining the security of your Personally Identifiable Information, we take precautions to safeguard your information through various procedures. We let you access your Personally Identifiable Information only after you enter the correct email ID and password. We keep the password encrypted to maintain security and we strongly recommend you to restrict the sharing of this password. 

To ensure complete safety of your personal information, we store it on a secure server that can only be accessed by some selected contractors and personnel. Here again, we encrypt all the sensitive information like the credit card details through the Secure socket Layer (SSL) system. 

Nonetheless, no data over any wireless network, especially on the Internet can ensure 100% guarantee. So no matter how sound and foolproof measures we adopt, we are unable to promise complete safety of any information transferred to or through our website. We cannot be held responsible for the disclosure of such information to the third parties at any time.

  3. Selection of Information by Users  
As stated earlier, you are always privileged with the right to filter the information on a website. If you do not wish to receive the promotional emails from our website, you can always opt-out. However, you will still continue to receive the administrative emails which relate to the purchases you made or your activities on the website. 

If you wish to discontinue promotional emails, you must choose the ‘opt-out’ option or by electing the ‘unsubscribe’ button’, which is present at the bottom of all the emails sent by us. 

  4. Tracking Data  
We employ the following practices to track data from our end users:

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are those small identifiers that we may transfer to the hard drive of your computer, to help the website administrator collect some non-personal information. We may use cookies to identify you when you visit our website again and to also know your response towards our site. Anyhow, cookies are not meant for extracting any kind of personal data from your system. To ensure your privacy, we don’t use cookies for storing or transferring your personal data on the World Wide Web. If you wish to remove cookies, you may do so by modifying your browser settings, but declining cookies may affect the functioning of certain parts of the website. 

**Other Devices**

The web beacons and pixel tags are some other standard technologies that are used for tracking information from website users. We may use these devices for updating our own data or else permit our third party service providers to use them. Both web beacons and pixel tags come in the form of small graphic images positioned at some pages of the website or in emails to let us determine the performance of a specific action at your end. When you open an email or browse a webpage, these tiny devices generate a note of your action. We simply use pixel tags to draw a better understanding of the behavior of our visitors and users while allowing us to evaluate the effectiveness of our promotional activities. Along with utilizing our own web beacons and pixel tags, we may also use the ones provided by our marketing partners or/and affiliates. 

  5. 5\. Third Party Privacy Policy  
Please note that this privacy policy solely controls the information collected by you on behalf of www.Lootbargain.com. All the other websites that may be linked with or be accessible via this website abide by their own privacy policies. So if you link-up with any such website, we recommend you to go through its privacy statement before using it. We have no control over the terms and policies of these third party websites and as such we are not liable for any action of these sites. 

**Open Communication Areas**

Certain sections of our website provide you with an option to post your information publicly while communicating with other users. Blogs, forums and discussion boards are the most common examples of such divisions that can be found in most of the websites. Additionally, if you submit some kind of media product or submit reviews (paid or unpaid) of products and services, your personal information may be visible to other visitors, users and companies. Now, we do not have any control over the postings that may come your way through such postings. When you submit your email address with a review or comment, other people may use it for sending you promotional emails. However, we do not publish your name with your reviews without obtaining your consent.

**Minors**

Children under 18 years of age may not access our website and we do not, knowingly, accept any minor as our user. We neither collect any personal information from children nor aim to attract them to our site. Lootbargain.com does not sell products and services to anyone below the age of 18. We do sell certain items to adults that are meant for children.

**Contact Us**

Please keep visiting Lootbargain.com for any update in the privacy policy and other terms of use. We are happy about your involvement with us and would appreciate your feedback. So stay connected with us at www.lootbargain.com

**Address:** G-80 Preet Vihar,  
Delhi - 110092, India.  
Email: [contact@lootbargain.com](mailto:contact@lootbargain.com)
